[opening theme music playing]
UPON A NEST OF DRIED NOODLES
DRAMA CLUB
[Fudge] We're off.
[Aoba] Bill, lock up when you're done.
FESTIVAL OF THE METEOR
[Bill] Sure thing! Just finishing up.
[sighs]
But before I do,
time for a little bite to eat.
[Bill humming]
ORIGINAL EGG-FLAVOR ABURA SOBA
[screams]
[tense breathing]
[Bill] No way...
Uh... It's gotta be dead.
[gasps]
So if I ate this... would that be bad?
Bill the Bengal Tiger,
you better think about this.
Devouring is a serious crime,
so that's why carnivores stick to getting
our protein from milk and eggs instead.
This is a tricky one.
Can I eat it? Or not?
Well, I mean, look.
This tiny thing's probably going to die.
I have to say...
[salivating]
It would probably be crazy delicious.
[Louis] Honestly, I couldn't care less
about you swallowing some animal blood
to pep yourself up.
[Bill] Apologies, buddy.
This is just who I am, Louis.
I'm a fan of instant gratification.
And if I'm being real with myself,
I half-ass everything.
I guess I'm just carnivore trash
who loves eating meat!
- [Pina] Are you going to eat that?
- [Bill exclaims]
- Wow, first time I've seen this.
- [grunts in frustration]
I've heard of situations like this
occasionally, but...
[stuttering] I thought you went home!
Ah, now I see.
You were hoping nobody would be around
to see you end that thing's life,
am I right?
[Bill seethes]
I'll be able to use this
when I play a carnivore.
[Bill grunting]
Go ahead, don't let me stop you.
- As if I'm not even here.
- Huh?
I'll be taking a few notes.
[Bill growls]
The world is strange...
It's unfair and cruel.
[Bill] Huh?
[Pina] Riz, for example, is sitting
in juvie right now for eating a classmate.
Meanwhile, you'll eat that thing,
and your peaceful life at school
continues on as if it never happened.
Of course I won't eat it!
Oh. If that's the case,
what are you going to do?
Save the thing, obviously!
Wow! Carnivores are amazingly complex.
I'm learning a lot.
[Bill growls]
I didn't realize you had
as many layers as you do stripes.
- You little...
- [chick squeaks]
- Hmm?
- Huh?
[squeaking weakly]
[Pina] Oh, boy.
[gentle music playing]
Ah...
[chuckles]
[Bill] You're all warm and cozy now,
I bet.
It says the parent bird's body heat is...
[chick squeaking]
It's burning!
[exclaims]
[grunting]
[squeaks]
Sure you weren't making yakitori?
Not funny, Pina.
But, speaking of yakitori,
what's this thing eat?
Let's see.
What does a baby chick eat?
A FEW DAYS LATER
[Kai] I mean, come on,
I just wish those two would cut it out.
[Fudge] Huh? Juno and Pina?
Yeah. The tension between them is totally
ruining the vibe, if you ask me.
Well, hopefully
those two will get all that sorted out.
If they don't, we're screwed.
[exclaims]
Sorry about that. My bad, you guys.
Hey! You know how much it would've cost
if you broke one of our lights?
Like it would've mattered.
You know the principal
would just buy you babies a new one.
What?
Everyone at school knows you rejects
are all the principal's little pets.
[laughs] Even after that devouring,
you little brats are still spoiled.
All you carnivores and herbivores
playing pretend.
So who's gonna be on the menu
at your next rehearsal?
[Kai] All right, enough!
Your paws are gonna look good
- shoved up your--
- [Bill] Cut it out!
Huh?
The drama club president's
here to save the day.
Have you guys had lunch yet?
[all exclaim]
Those look sharp.
Yeah. Time to go.
[basketball player laughing]
Don't know about you, but I like living.
We gotta keep our heads down.
Let's just focus on the show.
Yeah, but come on...
[Bill] Hurry up,
this stuff needs to get to the club room.
Hey, you're stronger than all of us.
Wanna lend a hand?
[Bill] I'm busy right now.
[Kai] I wonder what's going on with him.
I heard he spaced out in class,
and the professor called him on it.
And he hasn't been at his dorm much.
I bet it's got something
to do with a girl.
So who we talkin' about?
[Aoba, Fudge and Kai exclaim]
It felt like I saw the start
of an argument from over there. [chuckles]
I came over hoping to be entertained.
[Kai] It wasn't a show for you!
Oh, really?
Bill doesn't seem like himself lately.
[Fudge] He doesn't really strike me
as the broody type.
[Pina] Hmm.
- [Bill grunting]
- [scraping]
Hmm?
[frustrated sigh]
[Bill] Ugh, why is this so tough?
[chirping]
Sorry, I couldn't find very much today.
Don't choke on this, huh? Open up.
[gulps]
[chirping]
Yeah, I knew it wouldn't be enough.
[Pina] Apparently
they like eating rice too.
[exclaims] You scared me!
[Pina] Hello.
Aoba's the one that told me
they like rice.
[Bill grunts] You told Aoba?
I didn't tell him about your little guy.
I told him I only wanted to know
just in case the day came
when I happen to get a bird pregnant.
[sighs in relief] Thanks for that.
Would you look at that. Isn't it great?
Huh? What's great?
That it's looking healthy.
You are happy, right?
Of course I'm happy! However...
However?
- No, it's nothing.
- Hmm.
[Bill] You can go.
[Pina] I'm not here for this little bird,
I told you I'm observing you
for my acting research.
[Bill] It's weird seeing
your tender side come out.
[Pina] What? I'm just calm.
Sometimes I'm even able to scare myself,
but this bird has no idea what fear is.
[chick squeaks]
[Bill] Do you know how close I came
to eating you?
[chirps]
[Bill chuckles softly]
[Deshico] Ah, let's see...
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Mmm-hmm...
Ugh.
[spitting]
The east side is certainly no good.
Well, this is an off-year, remember.
But that doesn't mean
quality can have an off-year, too.
[inhales]
By the way, did the Shishi-Gumi
come to pay for the Melda?
No. They were busy
with the Masquerade Party,
then said they were short on cash.
And here I was thinking that
the lions would make a good target.
The problem is their leader, isn't it?
And speaking of,
I heard their boss is missing.
[chuckles]
There's a reason I've been doing so much
research into hybrids like him, you know.
We'll just have to make sure
that Melon takes responsibility.
[Corne] The first victim was a herbivore.
The culprit, a carnivore.
SUSPECT DEAD, VICTIM DEAD
[Corne] Then it was lights out
for that same carnivore.
Which brings us to this delightful case.
We're seeing the same pattern
pop up again.
The carnivore culprit
turns into the victim.
Are we seeing a vigilante
punishing devourers then?
[Corne sighs]
Maybe we have a psychic vigilante
who knew they'd be committing a devouring.
[mouse clicks]
[Corne] And in this morning's case,
our greatest hits again.
[mouse clicks]
- [mouse clicks]
- [Corne] Look what we have here.
[Yahya] Kines?
Their entire stock
was supposed to be discontinued.
So where are they getting their supply?
I've got a theory on the victims--
- [yelps]
- [thud]
[Corne groaning] I'm gonna feel that one.
Reason 100 I hate using a mouse.
Oh, that smarts.
[panting]
Ms. Seven!
[Seven] Huh?
[sighs in relief]
Legoshi, you came all the way to see me?
I took it upon myself to call him.
They say the more the merrier, right?
- Are you okay? I...
- Ah, I just discovered it.
That's all that happened.
This morning, when I stopped by the shop,
it was such an awful scene.
And so I ended up fainting
right on the spot.
Oh... Ms. Seven, are you hurt?
Ah, I'm fine. Not hurt at all.
[Legoshi sighs in relief]
That's great!
I hear the crime scene's weird.
The culprit devoured the shop clerk
and then was killed by someone else.
And whoever did it,
they still haven't found him or her.
[Legoshi] Wait, so, you're saying
there were two separate murders?
It seems the shop clerk
was devoured by her own lover.
An interspecies couple, yeah.
Oh...
[Seven] There's been a lot of devourings
lately between interspecies couples.
[Legoshi groans uneasily]
[Seven] It makes you wonder
if interspecies relationships
can ever be safe.
Or are they always deadly?
Well, I guess that's for them
to figure out themselves.
[sighs softly]
Yeah, you're right about that.
But anyway there's nothing to worry about.
I'm totally fine. Really.
Right.
I'm glad to hear that.
If you need some quiet time, I understand.
Yeah.
You show concern in a different way
than most carnivores do.
[Legoshi] Oh, uh...
It was sweet of you to check on me.
[Legoshi exclaims]
I've gotta make my way back to work.
I'm glad you're okay.
Call me if you need anything.
Bye!
[rushed footsteps]
Legoshi. Feelings make him bashful.
Ah.
[Lisa] Sorry for dragging you along.
Is this guy really that cool?
He's amazing.
I saw him on the news and I was like,
"Oh, there's my boy!"
So cool, and it doesn't hurt
that he's such a cutie.
- [Haru laughs]
- Ah, over there!
- [music playing]
- So, uh, what sport does he play?
[Lisa] Well, I don't think
he's really a sports guy...
Look! There he is!
What?
[host] All right, everyone!
Today's guest is our ambassador
for the Zoolympic bid,
and I can't think
of a better choice to represent us!
He's the heir of The Horns Conglomerate.
It's Louis the red deer!
It's a pleasure to be here.
I LOVE LOUIS
[host] We're all thrilled to be empowered
by the wisdom
I'm sure we'll receive from our guest.
Ready, and...
- Empower!
- [recording] Empower!
[Haru] I had no idea he'd been so...
public lately.
He's really in another galaxy now.
- I mean, he always was.
- [host] All right,
we've got some great questions
from our listeners! Question one.
Were you only chosen as ambassador
because you're related to a big sponsor?
[Louis] Not at all.
Just as we can't choose what species
we are before we're born,
we also can't choose our family, right?
It just so happens
that my father is chairman of Horns.
[recording] Empower!
Have you ever seen more amazing eyelashes?
I guess...
And I heard you had
your own fan club in high school?
Where'd you hear something like that?
I'm sure you were around all walks of life
in school, like carnivore ladies, right?
Well, some carnivore gals
made their way here to see you!
Someone's species
is really nothing more than an attribute.
In my opinion, the path
we choose to walk is what matters.
The choices we make as individuals,
not what species you happen to be.
[recording] Empower!
So great!
Now let's dig a little bit deeper.
[chuckles]
I'm gonna read an email we got. Uh...
"I'm afraid to tell my friends and family
I fell in love with a carnivore."
How would you handle this, Louis?
[soft music playing]
Well, I have a friend...
Huh?
- Their worry has been weighing on them.
- Hmm.
They're scared that
living the way they want
might cause trouble
for their parents or those close to them.
[host] Oh...
And they weren't sure if the thing
they actually wanted was worth
- all the trouble that would come--
- [recording] Empower!
Oh, I didn't mean to press that!
[chuckles] I don't think we missed
any wisdom from me.
[host] Okay! Let's move on to a request.
[Haru] All right, here we go.
[camera clicks]
Thank you. You're so sweet.
My pleasure.
[Lisa chuckling excitedly]
I can't believe you're actually friends
with him!
- [chuckling nervously]
- Since when?
All right, well, it's good to see you.
What? You're leaving?
Yeah, Lisa and I have shopping to do.
- [Lisa] Aw. We can go another time!
- Huh?
The mall's not going anywhere!
He's your friend, right?
- Well, it's just--
- Stop it. Just stay and chat him up!
Ah, he's busy! I thought we were shopping.
Oh, we can do it another day.
See you back at school.
- [Haru] Uh, okay...
- Later!
[Haru] Well, I guess... Bye!
It's kind of refreshing,
seeing you with a friend, Haru.
[scoffs] That's not rude at all.
I've had friends since elementary school.
I didn't mean to insult you.
[Louis] Wow... She might be just the person
I most wanted to see right now.
From the very beginning, with Haru,
I never had to be something I wasn't
with her.
Well, nice chatting with you.
What?
I... I need to get back. Assignments due.
Let me walk with you.
ODD SOUL FESTIVAL
[Haru] Isn't this
pretty far out of the way for you?
- [Louis] It's okay, it goes back around.
- Well, if you say so.
You know,
Legoshi told me he takes this bus,
even though his house
is nowhere near its route.
[both laugh]
[Louis] Stalker behavior.
Legoshi is such a weirdo sometimes.
But I like it. [laughs]
That's nice.
[Louis] It feels kind of strange.
There was a time her white fur
and innocent face were so delicate
I could've sworn she'd vanish
at any moment.
But now, this rabbit is so defined.
Even though you and I didn't
end up together,
I like the Haru you turned into.
Uh... Really?
Aren't I kind of a square?
- What do you mean?
- Uh...
Lately, I've been learning
to think before I leap.
Before, no matter what I did,
even if I got into trouble,
I'd just think,
"stuff happens,"
and threw caution to the wind.
But now I think...
"Is Legoshi worrying about me right now?"
Ah. Well, yeah,
that's definitely not like the old Haru.
Changing for some guy
seems kind of corny if you ask me.
Doesn't being able to change like that
prove it's a good relationship?
That's the corny stuff I'm talking about.
[sighs]
But then I get caught up in the moment.
[Melon groans]
They were serving corn soup
for lunch today. It gets caught...
[Haru exclaiming softly]
[Melon grunts softly]
I had my doubts
you and I would cross paths again.
Especially, of course, after being fired.
This might be the last time
we see each other.
Oh, uh, is that right? Sorry to hear that.
[Melon laughs]
If you're disappointed, I can't tell.
Weird question for you, Professor...
But are you mixed?
Carnivore and herbivore?
[Melon] Hmm, how to respond to that...
People who ask that
usually end up with a frown on their face.
[chuckles excitedly]
So then mixes can grow up
healthy and strong!
Amazing! I'm so glad!
I was thrilled!
Because, you know, like,
if Legoshi and I wanted to have a child,
it sounds like it'd be okay, right?
Wait, uh, back up...
Was he a mix of gazelle and leopard?
[Haru] Yeah, you know, horns and all.
They go up and out like this.
[Louis] Oh, that... uh--
[Haru] Uh-huh. And he's got these...
[Melon laughing]
Somebody being happy I was born
is certainly a new one for me.
I must say, you're really quite unusual.
What? No way. It's normal.
We all celebrate birthdays.
[Melon grunts softly]
Well... [inhales]
No one's ever celebrated mine before.
No?
It's on the same day as a festival.
Oh, I see.
What are you gonna do, right?
The Odd Soul Festival.
A day to be thankful that herbivores
weren't eaten by carnivores. Eh.
Ironic, that a mix like me
was born on that day.
So your birthday's coming up soon then?
Do you have a birthday wish?
You've gotta treat yourself!
[Melon sighs demurely] Oh...
You might be right.
Hmm. What I really want is...
[Haru] Yeah, yeah, I'm listening.
What?
He said that he wants to eat your flesh?
STOPPING
So, what did you say back then?
I said, "Sure."
- Huh?
- [chuckling nervously]
I was caught off guard.
Oh, uh... [chuckles nervously]
A pinky promise?
Uh... [chuckles nervously]
Okay, you got it.
[laughs]
Are you supposed to be some kind
of convenience store snack?
[Haru] Oh, that's harsh.
I'm more like a fancy desert
at a fine dining restaurant.
Anyway, I'm fine being the kind of girl
who gives rather than takes.
Herbivores are meant to be eaten, right?
I never thought that one day I'd be
dealing with your prenuptial doubts.
[Haru grunting]
You're neither a snack, nor a dessert.
You're neither herbivore,
nor are you prey.
You are Haru. You're just yourself.
Complain all you like.
Cry about it. Whatever.
But you have to keep living.
You have to live!
I don't need you bossing me around.
- Goodbye.
- [Louis exclaims]
Wait! Haru!
CENTRAL BUS SHIOKUMIZAKAUE
There were tons of blueberries
growing behind the fountain,
so I picked these.
Uh-- Oh.
[Pina sighs softly]
Hey, Bill? What's going on? You okay?
It was so full of life.
Now it's just cold and still.
[gentle music playing]
[Bill] I'm sorry.
There was a power outage.
And because of that,
its heat lamp shut off.
If it was going to die anyway,
maybe you should've eaten it
right from the start.
[Pina grunts]
[groans softly]
[grunts]
Not funny.
[Pina] If you think about
eating and loving,
both of them should bring us happiness.
But when those two things intertwine,
someone always ends up getting hurt.
[closing theme song playing]